# Prannoy Lal

✓prannoy.lal@uwaterloo.ca ♠github.com/PrannoyLal ♠linkedin.com/in/PrannoyLal ♣(905) 598-4636

# SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

#### General

Proven leader from experience as DECA President & BMYC Director.

Exceptional interpersonal communication abilities, developed from tutoring Kumon students, marketing for BMYC & contacting sponsors for UW AFSA.

Familiar with the Agile framework and applied it with success on DECA Executive team.

#### **Tools**

High proficiency with Microsoft Office, Git, Bash, SQL, Latex and Photoshop

## **PROJECTS**

#### **Portfolio Analytics Visualization**

Built a front-end application that displayed various financial ratios of a security portfolio.

# Employmint - 1st Place at AlphaHacks 2017

Android application that serves as a job network for teenagers aged 14-18. Created business plan and pitch for hack.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Waterloo**

Computing and Financial Management, 2018-2023

Relevant courses: AFM101: Intro to Financial Accounting, AFM102: Intro to Managerial Accounting, AFM121: Intro to Global Financial Markets

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Kumon Learning Centre**

Math and Reading Tutor

Aug 2015 – Aug 2017 Brampton, ON

- Effectively educated 200+ students in the fields of math and English with a holistic perspective.
- Marked and recorded student completed worksheets and tests with strong attention to detail.

## LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

**UW Accounting & Finance Student Assoc.** Sep 2018 - Present External Relations Committee Member Waterloo, ON

• Successfully communicated with external organizations (e.g. Tim Hortons) obtain sponsorship for 2 on-campus events

# Harold M. Brathwaite DECA President

March 2016 – June 2018 Brampton, ON

- Handled accounts in excess of \$20,000
- Increased chapter membership by 375% from 40 students to 150 students.
- Vastly improved chapter performance at regional (from 6 ribbons in 2016 to 59 ribbons and 11 medals in 2017) and provincial competitions (from 0 medals in 2016 to 25 medals in 2017) through new work-shop based training system.

# **Brampton Multicultural Youth Council**Director of Marketing

June 2016 - June 2018 Brampton, ON

- Scripted, storyboarded & filmed a Youtube video series about multiculturalism.
- Lead marketing committee to organize 5 unique monthly social media campaigns.

## **AWARDS**

**Top 12 Finalist - DECA Provincial Competition** Feb 2018 Placed in top 12 out of 130 in the Retail Merchandising Series category.

**1st Place - Canada's Wonderland Pitch Competition** Aug 2017 Pitched a new addition to Canada's Wonderland to marketing executives. Organized by the Ivey Summer Leadership Program, UWO.

Winning Venture - Dragon's Nest Jan 2016

Pitched a visual-merchandising baking company to a panel of investors.